<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.jastemf.converter"
      label="JastEMF Ecore - AST Converter"
      version="0.1.0"
      provider-name="Software Technology Group - TU Dresden">

   <description url="http://www.jastemf.org">
      
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2010, TU Dresden, Christoff Bürger, Sven Karol
 All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
      documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    * The name of the authors may not be used to endorse or promote products
      derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO
EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.mwe.core" version="0.7.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.ant" version="1.7.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ant.core" version="3.2.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.5.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xpand" version="0.7.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.mwe.utils" version="0.7.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtend" version="0.7.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtend.typesystem.emf" version="0.7.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.jastemf" version="0.1.4" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.commons.logging" version="1.1.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.emf.codegen" version="2.6.0.v20100914-1218"/>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.emf.codegen.ecore" version="2.6.1.v20100914-1218"/>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.emf" version="2.6.1.v20100914-1218"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.jastemf.converter"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
